**Dongshen Wang**3110 Richview Blvd, Oakville, ON, Canada • (905) 466-4091 • dwshen2023@gmail.com

# **SUMMARY**

Computer engineering graduate with industry experience in web development and testing. Strong passion for learning and self-improvement.

- Programming languages: C, Python, Java, C#, Swift, TypeScript
- Tools: Angular, XCode, Ubuntu CLI, Docker, Git, SwiftUI, Android Studio

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Transport Canada** Ottawa, ON

RPA developer

May 2022 - March 2023

- Collaborated in client meetings to collect workflow requirements and propose automated processes to help improve workflow efficiency.
- Developed a UiPath bot that can upload scanned files through an online portal. Successfully uploaded more than 4000 files and reduced 133 hours of repetitive manual tasks.
- Demonstrated an automated process's functionality and presented its business value during the department's monthly tech day.

# **Mitel Networks Corporation**

Ottawa, ON

E2E Automation Tester

Sept. 2021 – Dec. 2021

- Built end-to-end test case with Protractor automation framework to ensure the PBX API phone dial feature's function correctness and robustness.
- Ran automation testing with AWS to reduce wait time and used the Cloudwatch to capture test results.

**Morgan Stanley** Montreal, QC

Full Stack Developer

Jan. 2021 - Apr. 2021

- Created ETL dashboard element for web API to record task status and notify developers when errors occur.
- Worked with Kanban and Jira to follow the Agile development cycle and ticket tracking.

# **PROJECTS**

Scrum meeting iOS app with Visual time management

*April* 2023 – May 2023

- Programmed an app to make scrum meetings short and focused by using visual cues to indicate meeting duration and time left for current the speaker.
- Created the app's front-end UI, four main scenes and other sub-views, using the SwiftUI framework. Familiarized with the framework's view and navigation's hierarchy.
- Worked with property wrappers, concurrency, and JSON to store persist data.

Intelligent distribution panel simulation

September 2022 – November 2022

- Led a group of 6 in a project-based course as scrum master, managed weekly scrums, unit and integration test following test procedures and sprint documents provided by the professor.
- Developed and tested relay timer and continuous data analysis and acquisition module using C and Sitara MCU SDK. Achieved final project grade of 94/100.

# **EDUCATION**

University of Ottawa

Third- and fourth-year GPA: 3.7/4

Graduation date: January 2023

Bachelor of Applied Science – Computer Engineering

2020 & 2022 Dean's list honours student

Related Courses: Higher Layer Network Protocol, Data structure and algorithm, Digital System, Computer System Design, Operating System, Software Construction, Computer Architecture